意大利罗马
我要进去了
I'm going in.
哦
Oh!
美国密西西比州
理智
There is
和疯狂之间
an impossibly fine line
只有一线之隔
between sanity and madness.
我们并不总能知道
And it's not always possible to know
自己是在这条线的哪一边
which side of that line we are standing on.
双方之间的冲突
The violence between disparate sides
并不是这种文化特有的
is not endemic to this culture.
它是所有文化共有的
it is endemic to all cultures.
我们依然是
We are again
族群
tribes.
但是定义
But defining
我们的族群
our tribe is not as simple
并不像出生在阳光下的黑人
as the black people born under the sun,
或者出生在月光下的白人那么泾渭分明
or the white people born under the moon.
我们的分裂在于
Our division is,
认为别人是错的
wrong others
自己是对的
against right self.
这种分裂
And this division does not rest
不仅仅是因为我们对自己以外的族群
simply on an unfamiliarity
不熟悉
with a tribe other than our own.
比那更深
It's deeper than that.
先生?
Sir?
请讲
Yes?
现在是21 世纪了 麦克莱斯博士
It's the 21st century, Dr. Mackles.
有了手机 我可以了解
With my phone, I can learn about
这个星球上的任何文化
any culture on the planet.
我用20分钟就能了解
I'm a Google search away from knowing
任何一个信仰体系
everything about a belief system in 20 minutes.
我来问你一个问题
Let me ask you a question.
假如你搜索到的信仰体系
What if that belief system you Googled
与你的信仰完全对立
was so antithetical to your own,
那么你会不会觉得他们是…
that would seem, for lack of a better word,
疯子?
insane?
什么信仰体系
Like what?
比如
Well, like, uh,
比如说药
take medicine.
在美国 所谓药物
Here, medicine is
都是在实验室
all pharmaceutical compounds
制造的药物化合物
created in laboratories,
由不露面的公司卖给无数人
sold by faceless corporations to millions.
在世界上有些地方
In other parts of the world,
药是植物
medicine is a plant.
一 块树皮 一根树根
A bit of bark, a root,
或者一种矿物质
or a mineral.
或者所有这些的组合
Or a combination of all of them.
而医生
Administered to one man
拥有着
by another man
普通人理解不了的
who is believed to channel powers
灵异功能
that you could not begin to comprehend.
这种医学知识是基于古老的信仰
This medical knowledge is based on ancient beliefs.
他们的教义在美国人听来
The tenets of which in this country,
只会毛骨惊然
it would just make your blood run cold.
治疗和人性中的抽象信仰
Metaphysical beliefs in healing and humanity.
这在你看来
That would seem, um,
是疯狂的
insane to you,
使你完全无法理解
no matter how hard you tried to understand them.
而这种药物
But it is the very belief in such things
又讲究信则灵
that gives this medicine it's power.
时间到了
Looks like we're out of time.
我们下周继续
So, we'll take this up again next week.
谢谢
Thank you.
霍布斯同学
Mr. Hobbs.
我想让你为我做点事
I want you to do something for me.
如果你愿意做 可以加分
A little extra credit, if you will.
我要你用你的手机
I want you to take that phone in your pocket
找一种与你的文化完全相反的文化
and find me a culture that is so inverse to your own
而且还在这个城市扎根
that the idea of it taking root here, in this city,
让你毛骨悚然
would scare the bejesus out of you.
是
Yes, sir.
进去
Get the fuck in there!
别动
Don't fucking move.
不要 等等
No! Wait!
-喂 -住手
-Hey! Stop!
你在里面做什么
What are you doing in there?
我是博伊德警探
I'm Detective Boyd.
离我远点
Get away from me!
-冷静一下 -我不想走
-Calm down, it's okay. I don't wanna go.
求你了
Please?
他要把她怎么样? 她是我的
No. What's he doing with her? That's mine!
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
你不能带走她
You can't take her!
我是博伊德警探
I'm Detective Boyd.
-她是我的 -别和她说话
-She's mine! Don't talk to her!
来吧 把手给我
Come on, give me you hand.
你要把她怎么样
What are you doing with her?
举起手来
Keep your hands up!
我带你出去 走吧
Look, I'm gonna get you outta here. Come on.
-玛丽亚 -喂 你要去哪里?
-Maria? -Hey, where are you going?
-玛丽亚 -你要去哪里?
-Maria? -Where you going?
你不能带走她
You can't take her!
喂
Hey, man.
她是我的人
Get on your fucking--She stays with me, pal.
现在站起来
Get down on your feet now.
我没做什么坏事
I didn't do anything wrong, man.
-是吗 -她自愿跟我来的
-Yeah? -She came willingly with me.
我说了你站起来
I told you, get on your fucking feet!
不 你去死吧
Nah! You go to hell, bitch.
你先来
You first.
不 不
No, no, no, no!
要抓活的
We need him alive!
医务人员正在路上
Medics are on the way.
你去死吧
Then go to hell!
你先来
You first.
法纳先生
Mr. Farner.
兰德先生 很荣幸
Mr. Randoku. It is an honor, sir.
你已经这么有权势
A man like you, who is so powerful.
为何还要做这个?
Tell me, why do you want to do this?
我们是谁在询问谁?
Who is interviewing who?
是我在询问你 先生
I am interviewing you, sir.
我不是跟任何人都做生意
I do not do business with anyone,
必须是我很了解的人
I do not know everything about.
我也一样
Neither do I.
兰德先生 我是一个寻求
Mr. Randoku, I'm a man who explores options
各种力量的人
of power, as you say.
难以得到
It is elusive.
而你是一个收集力量的人
You are a man who harvests power,
还储存着
and bottles it even.
你现在也在被很多人调查
You're also a man with a lot of eyes on you right now.
我有架飞机可以送你去任何地方
I have a plane that can take you anywhere you like.
你客气了 先生
Appreciate the kind words, sir.
但我不需要你的帮助
I do not need your help.
是你需要我
You… need me.
你准备好了联系我
Let me know when you are ready.
想想你能在那里收集的灵魂吧 兰德先生
Think of the souls you could've harvested there, Mr. Randoku.
博伊德警探 当你向嫌犯开枪时
Detective Boyd, did you feel any sense of vindication
你有没有觉得不应该?
when you fired at the suspect?
不杀他 他就会杀了我
Other than it was him or me? No.
你向普雷斯顿先生开枪的决定
Did the death of your own daughter in any way
有没有受到你女儿之死的任何影响?
affect your decision to fire on Mr. Preston?
没有
No.
说实话 卡农女士
Let's be honest, Ms. Cannon.
开枪时 普雷斯顿先生
Mr. Preston was clearly leaning forward
明显身体前倾
at the time of the shooting,
伸手去拿枪
reaching for a gun.
还有别的问题吗
Any more questions?
你还好吗
You okay?
是的
Yeah.
这没有说服力
That's not convincing.
我没事
No, I'm okay.
我又做了一个噩梦
I had another bad dream.
你想谈谈吗?
Do you want to talk about it?
不 不想谈
No. Not really.
喂?
Hello?
是我
Yes, it' s me.
我们开始吧
Let's move forward.
我会把约定的数额汇给你
I'll wire what we agreed upon.
快快快
Go, go, go, go, go!
你能行
You got it!
好 你先进去
All right, you go first.
我开玩笑的
I'm just kidding. Yeah.
怎么了
What's going on?
你可能骗过了审查委员会
You might have fooled the review board,
别以为能骗得了我
but don't you think you can fool me.
知道了 知道了
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
现在你
Now, you get your ass
去心理医生那里 看看能不能骗过她
over to the shrink and see if you can fool her.
我听不见你在说什么
I think I'm having a hard time hearing you
脑子里有各种幻听
'cause all I can hear are the voices.
知道吗
You know?
你开心了?
Fuckers… You having fun?
是的 特别开心
Yeah, loads.
我在想也许你应该去度个假
I was thinking maybe you should take a vacation.
-是吗 -是的
-Oh, yeah? -Yeah.
你会劝我去哪里度假?
I'm just curious. Where would you send me?
只要不是这里
Anywhere but here.
去做什么
And do what?
随便 钓鱼
I don't know. Fish.
去租一艘船
Go out on -a charter boat. -Fish?
把鱼饵扔到水里
Drop a line in the water.
玛丽亚 这也太无聊了
Maria, that sounds fucking horrible.
你需要它
Well, you need it.
你老实跟我说
Between you and I -and just us. -Yeah?
他真的伸手去拿枪了吗
Was he really going for his gun?
玛丽亚 我来问你
Maria, let me ask you a question.
你觉得会有人怀念杀人狂吗
Do you think anybody misses Ted Bundy?
你没回答我
That's not an answer.
我回答了 是你没认真听
No. It is, if you're listening.
去你的
Fuck that.
要我来应答?
You want me to get that?
-好 -130号警车正前往
-Yeah, you get that. -This is 130 reporting.
什么情况 吉米?
What do we got, Jimmy?
浮尸 白人女性
A floater. Caucasian female.
死了大概6个小时
She's been dead, maybe 6 hours.
我的天
Oh, fuck.
死者身份?
Any ID?
不知道
No. Nothing.
年龄?
Age?
大概14-15岁
Maybe 14, 15.
有人对她下了狠手
Somebody did a real number on her.
她的手 生殖器都被切除了
Her hands, genitals have been removed.
你是说被螃蟹吃了?
You mean, crabs got to her?
野生动物不会吃这些部位
You don't lose the parts she's missing to wildlife.
她在被抛户前被割伤了
She was cut before she was dumped.
就算不是手术刀 那也是一样锋利的东西
If it wasn't a scalpel, it was something just as sharp.
眼睛 眼睑
Eyes, eyelids.
是的
Yeah.
左手 都切掉了
Left hand, missing.
没了
Gone.
这就是她的死因吗 比尔?
You think that's what killed her, Bill?
不 死因是这个
No. Death was a courtesy of this.
割喉 失血过多
Throat cut. Bled out.
她的血管里充满了河流於泥
Her veins are full of river silt.
我们只发现了她的 DNA
The only DNA we found was that of hers.
这些伤痕
And these marks.
看看这些
Look at these.
就像某种绳子
It's like some kind of rope.
把她倒吊起来
Hung by her feet.
就像吊一块牛肉
Like a side of beef.
天
Goddamn.
这依然线索不足
This isn't getting any better.
-我会查到更多 -好
I'll know more later. All right.
谢谢你 医生 你能帮我把它送到楼上吗
Thanks, doc. Can you send it upstairs for me?
-好的 -谢谢
Yeah. Thank you.
-你没事吧? -嗯?
-You okay? -Hmm?
-你没事吧? -是的 我没事
-Are you okay? -Yeah, I'm fine.
给我一点时间
Just give me a second.
可能是黑帮…
All right, gang related or…
不 这和黑帮无关
No, no, no, no. This ain't gang related.
是吗
No?
做的有条不紊 有明确目的性
It's more methodical. Somebody with a purpose.
得了 有目的性
Yeah. With a purpose, right?
拜托 博伊德 你可不能确定
Come on, Boyd. You don't know that yet.
万一他是对的呢
What if he's right?
他对过什么
About what?
你还有其他更好的线索
You have other cases with so much better leads.
现在做好你的工作 出去吧
Now just do your job. Get the hell out of here.
-警长? -嗯?
Captain? -Yeah?
你没看到她的样子
You didn't see what she looked like.
你在想什么
What are you thinking?
我在想又一个好警察变成了官僚
I'm thinking another good cop became a bureaucrat.
我请你喝一杯怎么样?
Well, how about I buy you a drink?
听起来不错
Sounds great.
哦
Ooh!
喂 砸框了
Yo! That's a brick!
喂 传给我 我这边空了
Oh, come on, dude! Hit me! I'm open! I'm open!
三不沾
Air ball!
投篮 投篮
Shoot it! Shoot it!
犯规了
I think that's a foul!
你太差劲了 兄弟
Oh, you suck, bro.
喂 传给我
Hey, pass it to me.
漂亮
Yes! Yes!
他投中了
He did it!
为什么不让我打?
Why didn't you let me play?
杰米只会砸框 啥都投不进
You know Jamie shoots nothing but bricks.
该走了 弟弟
It's time to go, little bro.
等等 我要去哪里?
Wait. Where am I going?
你要回家了
Well, you're going home.
可我想和你一起玩
But I wanna play with you.
你要回家了 不早了
You're going home. It's getting late.
妈妈会担心的 你还有作业
Mom's gonna be worried. You know, you got homework.
你就从来不做作业
But you never did your homework.
我没你成绩好
I'm not as smart as you.
你聪明 别浪费了
You got a brain. You can use it.
你需要去学习
You need to go study.
去吧
Come on.
灌死你
Dunk it up your ass.
喔
Whoo!
不 放开我
No, let me go!
放我出去
Let me out of here!
这球员很棒
This kid is great.
是真的 他…
That is fucking, it's true and he--
他一直就是不控球
He continuously just does not run the ball.
你知道 你不需要
You know, you don't have to be dealing
办理这种案子 毕竟…
with something like this, after…
毕竟什么 你什么意思?
After what? What do you mean?
你知道的 卢卡斯
You know, Lucas.
天啊
Oh, Christ.
你是说我女儿吗
Are you talking about my daughter?
是的 另外…
Well, yeah. And…
玛丽亚 那事不会影响我
Maria, I'm dealing with it the best way I know how.
如果我处在你这种情况
I'm just saying, if it were me,
我会立刻离开
I'd be gone in a heartbeat.
你不是这种情况 我也不像你
Well, it ain't you. And I'm not you.
拜托
Come on now.
我不是心理医生
I'm no shrink.
没错 你不是心理博士
That's for fucking sure, you aren't a shrink.
怎么了
What?
-我只想做你的朋友 -谢谢
-I'm just gonna be your friend. -Thank you.
好
Okay.
很棒 你知道朋友会做什么吗
Be great. You know what friends do?
会喝白酒
They order shots.
-你何不请我喝一杯? -好
Why don't you -buy me a shot? -Okay.
-我们喝几杯白酒 -好吧
Get us -a couple of shots. -Okay.
-来吧 -好吧
Okay? Come on. Fine.
Humu mimi nitakamata tani.
Humu mimi kuwa tani.
大约在凌晨一点钟接到他失踪的报案
He was called in missing about one a.m.
一些孩子在这里看到了他
Some kids found him here.
他妻子说 他出去钓鱼 但从不超过10点
Wife said, he goes out fishing, but never out past 10:00.
我估计他是看到了
My guess is that he came upon something
不该看到的东西
he wasn't supposed to see.
是的 还有别的吗
Yeah. Anything else?
是的 还有
Oh, yeah. There's more.
你过来看看
You're gonna wanna see this.
Mimi nitakamata tani.
Humu mimi kuwa tani.
什么情况 尼克?
What do we got, Nick?
西班牙裔男性 10岁左右
Hispanic male, about 10 years old.
和我们昨天在河边看到的尸体一模一样
Looks exactly like what we saw at the river yesterday.
操
Shit.
尼克 请务必给我一张照片
Nick, make sure I get a picture of that, please.
好
Okay.
就凭喉呢被割破
The old man would've died anyway
他也会流血而死
from his throat being cut,
只不过他已经没有心脏可以供血了
if he'd had a heart left to pump the blood out.
什么
What?
他的心脏被切得很干净
His heart had been sliced out clean,
他的喉呢里没有血
and there was no blood in his throat.
所以不管是谁干的 都非常快
So whoever did this, it was awfully quick.
你说的快 有多快?
I mean, when you say quick, like, how quick?
心脏被挖出来的时候还在跳动
I mean, like his heart might've still been beating.
但是那心脏呢 你找到了吗
But what about the heart? Did you find it?
没有
No.
-没有吗 -没找到
No? -No. Didn't find it.
那个男孩怎么样了?
What about the boy?
这个男孩跟第一个女孩一样
Well, the boy was like the first girl.
-是吗 -残缺不全
-Yeah? -Mutilated.
身体部位被切掉 没找到
Parts cut off. Missing.
有一点 这个人用的刀具
One thing. Whatever this guy is using,
锋利无比
is sharp as hell.
好
Okay.
想喝一杯吗
Want a little snoot?
这里有些上好的威士忌
Got some good whiskey here.
好 我喝一杯
Yeah, I'll take a little snoot.
还有一个…
And there's another, uh…
有意思的东西
another thing interesting.
是吗
Yeah?
还记得你从祭坛上带来的那些东西吗
Remember those things you brought from the altar?
是的
Yes, sir.
呃
Well…
干杯
Cheers.
这一个…
This one…
这是金粉
It's finely powdered gold.
什么金子?
What do you mean, gold?
诺克斯堡的金子
Like Fort Knox Gold.
没错
No shit.
还有这些…
And these…
-这些是你带来的草药 -是吗
These are some -herbs you brought. -Yeah?
我鉴定出其中一种了
I've been able to ID one of 'em.
这个是…
And it's, uh,
一种叫做rooibos的东西
something called rooibos.
是什么
What's that?
有一些关于它的研究
Well, there's been some research on it.
它来自非洲 这是一种红茶
It's from Africa. It's a red tea.
但不是你这种茶
Mmm. It ain't that kinda tea though.
谢谢你 比尔
Thanks, Bill.
不是你喝的这种
Not like you drink.
你好
Shit. Excuse me.
你知道麦克莱斯博士的办公室在哪里吗
Do you know where Dr. Mackles' office is?
-那边 -在这边吗
-That way. -It's back this way?
-是的 -天
-Yeah. -Gosh.
请进
Come in.
我能帮你吗
May I help you?
希望如此
Well, I hope so.
你是麦克莱斯博士吗
Are you Dr. Mackles?
是的
Yes.
我是区杀组警探卢卡斯·博伊德
I'm homicide detective Lucas Boyd.
我能坐下吗
Do you mind if I sit?
你教非洲研究 对吗
So, you teach African studies, is that right?
是的
Yes.
你来自非洲吗
Are you from Africa?
是的 莱索托
Yes. Lesotho.
莱索托是在哪里?
Where is that at?
它是南非的国中之国
It's a small country in the heart of South Africa.
哦
Oh.
我是非洲人重要吗
Is my being African important?
希望如此
Well, again, I hope so.
你知道rooibos是什么吗
Do you, uh, know what rooibos is?
是的 是茶
Yes. It's tea.
只是茶吗
Just tea?
它有时被用作药物
Well, it's sometimes used medicinally.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
闻闻这个 告诉我是什么 好吗
Um, smell this, and tell me what it is, will you?
你从哪里得到这个的?
Where did you get this?
怎么了 这是什么
Why? What is it?
麦克莱斯博士 这是什么
Dr. Mackles. What is it?
这是草药
It's… herbs.
是哪种草药?
Mmm-hmm. Just any kind of herbs?
我觉得是育亨宾树皮
Well, I would say yohimbe bark
还有一些其他发酵的树根
and, uh, some other fermented tree roots.
嗯
Hmm.
你从哪弄来的?
Where'd you get it?
我在犯罪现场找到的
I found it at a crime scene.
什么样的犯罪?
What kind of crime?
我是凶杀案侦探 先生
Well, I'm a homicide detective, sir.
你能告诉我这些文字是什么吗
Can you tell me what these writings are?
你可以很容易地搜索这个 侦探
You could easily google this, Detective.
我知道 我搜索过了
I know. I know. And I actually did.
完全看不懂
It didn't make sense to me.
但当我搜索
But then I did Google
非洲文化领域的顶尖学者时 看到了你的名字
leading scholars in African culture, and your name came up,
是顶尖级专家
as the best and brightest.
于是我就来了
So, here I am.
对不起 我帮不了你
I'm sorry. I cannot help you.
耽误你的时间了 先生
Well, I appreciate your time, sir.
-我们没犯什么罪 警探 -你们从不犯罪啊
你来逮捕我?
不是的
我只是在找个人
I'm just looking for someone.
一个幽灵
A ghost.
我想知道这个人的名字
I need to put a name to this face.
我在附近见过他
I've seen him around.
很好
Great.
他是一些奇特区杀案的主要嫌疑人
He's my main suspect in some strange killings.
我们找到了一个祭坛
We found an altar.
血祭
Blood.
我不知道这是什么意思
I don't really know what it means.
他是个桑格玛
He's a Sangoma.
桑格玛?
Sangoma?
接触过上帝
Touched by God.
一个巫医
A witch doctor.
他为客户工作
He works for clients.
什么样的客户?
What kind of clients?
有钱有势的
Rich and powerful ones.
我可以给你一点建议吗
May I give you a word of advice?
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
小心点
Be careful.
他可能会去找你
He could be coming for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
一切都好吗
Is everything okay?
麦克莱斯博士 我需要你的帮助
Dr. Mackles, I need your help.
两个孩子都死了
God dam it, two kids are dead.
他们像猪一样被屠杀
They were butchered like hogs.
你知道这些文字是什么吧
You know what these writings are, don't you?
拜托了
Now, please,
再看一眼
take another look.
我帮不了你
I cannot help you.
帮不了还是不愿帮?
Can't or won't?
你害怕 是吗
You're scared, aren't you?
小心脚下 博士
Watch your step, doctor.
哦
Oh.
这是什么 博士?
What is it, doctor?
是斯瓦希里语
It's Swahili.
祖鲁人
Zulu.
嗯
Hmm.
它代表领地
It identifies territory.
什么领地?
Identifies how?
力量的中心 或者….
Uh, centers of power, or…
获取那种力量的方法
ways to get access to that power.
帮我一个忙你 能看懂那个吗
Do me a favor. Can you read that right there?
看懂个大概
Well, roughly.
呃 "我获得力量
Uh, "Here I take the power.
"我成为力量"
"Here I become the power."
这个人是个桑戈玛
Your man is a Sangoma.
会医术的
A medicine man.
在你们的文化中 你会称他为巫医
In your culture, you would call him a witch doctor.
从他杀人的方式看 是这样
The way he's killing, that makes sense.
你听说过"Muti"这个词吗 警探
You ever hear the term "Muti," Detective?
没有
No.
是祖鲁语 意思是药
It's Zulu. It means medicine.
但是 Muti也有阴暗面
But, Muti has a dark side.
你是说他在用人体器官做药物?
So, are you saying that he is using the body parts for medicine?
没错
Exactly.
哦
-Right. -Well,
制药公司
you know, pharmaceutical companies
用流产胎儿的干细胞制造疫苗
use stem cells from aborted fetuses to create vaccines.
哦
Right.
这只是这个概念的
Well, this is just a primitive version
原始版本
of that concept.
你接着说
I'm listening.
从抽象的角度来看
Well, in a metaphysical sense,
这可以与所谓的
it can be tied to what can be referred to
"勇士传统"联系起来
as "the warrior tradition."
简而言之 这是一种按顺序进行的祭祀
Put simply, it's a ritual performed to order.
使一个人成为勇士
To make one a warrior,
或者给勇士提供力量
or to provide power to that warrior.
桑格玛斯施行Muti已经有几个世纪了
Sangomas have been practicing Muti for centuries.
商人 政治家 推销员 你
Businessmen, politicians, salesmen, you,
任何人
anyone.
为Muti付费的人是为了
People who pay for Muti are seeking
寻求个人成功
personal success,
权力
power,
保护
protection.
他们相信Muti能增强他们的个人力量
They believe that Muti strengthens their personal force,
给了他们优势
gives them an edge.
Muti对某些特定身体部位
In Muti, specific body parts
有明显的效果
have a distinct effect.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
生殖器
Genitals,
能带来阳刚之气和好运
they bring virility, good luck.
-尤其是处子之身 -哦
Especially if -they're virgin. -Right.
眼睛 视力可及远
The eyes, farsightedness,
视野清晰
clarity of vision.
大脑
The brain,
知识 政治权力
knowledge, political power.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
桑戈玛为了某个特定的结果
The Sangoma takes whatever they need
什么器官都要
for a specific outcome.
-我的天 -还不止如此
-Jesus Christ. -But, there's more.
桑戈玛必须在受害者还活着的时候
A Sangoman must take the flesh
取走其器官
while the victim is still alive…
对
Right.
为了得到他们寻求的力量
In order to get the power they seek…
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
他们必须唤醒众神来赐予它
…they must awaken the gods to bestow it.
这意味着
Which means…
受害者的惨叫声
the screams of the victim…
哦
Right.
至关重要
…are critical.
惨叫声越强烈
The more intense the scream,
Muti的效果就越好
the more powerful the Muti.
然后身体部位和受害者的血混合在一起
Then the body parts are mixed with the victim's blood,
草药 粘土 黄金
herbs, clay, gold,
所有这些都被认为
all of which is believed
能吸引和掌控力量
to attract and hold power.
客户或桑格玛喝下了炼金药
That elixir is drunk by the client or the Sangoma,
来得到他们寻求的力量
in order to get the power they seek.
他们相信这会把他们变成勇士
They believe that it turns them into a warrior.
使他们成为勇士
Makes them a warrior.
而且是不可战胜的
And an undefeatable one.
我是不相信
Sounds unbelievable to me.
是的 你是不信 警探
Right. To you, Detective.
对他来说 这只是生意 而且生意很好
To him, it's simply business. And very real.
生意很好
Very real.
不管他在做什么
Whatever he's about to do,
感觉他需要力量才能做到
it feels he needs power to do it.
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
你要知道
And understand this.
前两个人
These first two,
只是他的热身
they were just him getting ready.
他是为自己做的
He did them for himself.
明白吗
Capisce?
你真的相信这个吗
Do you really believe in this?
嗯 是的
Mmm-hmm. Yes.
这太变态了
This is just too sick.
但能让很多人相信是真实的
I mean, Maria, it's sick enough to be real, you know.
我只希望我能看到这个混蛋的脸
I just wish I could see this motherfucker's face.
我现在只看到一个恶人
All I see right now is a monster.
我想要一个漂亮的 一个有漂亮眼睛的
I want one that's beautiful. One with pretty eyes.
一个充满生机和希望的
One filled with life and promise.
我希望她有很高的智商
Oh, I want her to have a great deal of intelligence.
有美好前程的
And so much more to live for.
欢迎光临
Welcome.
-要什么酒 -龙舌兰酒
What can I -get for you? -Tequila.
纯的 还是加冰块的?
Neat, or on the rocks?
-纯的 -好
Neat. Okay.
你是新来本市?
Are you new in town?
是的
Yes.
旅游?
Vacation?
-不 工作 -嗯
-No, work. -Mmm.
你的口音很好听
That's a really cool accent.
是哪里的口音?
I like it. Where is it from?
我去过很多地方
I've been so many places.
很难说哪里
It is hard to say.
我能说实话吗
May I be honest?
好的
Oh, sure.
我喜欢你的眼睛
I like your eyes.
谢谢
Thank you.
-很美丽 -别说了
They are lovely. Stop it.
我是真心的
I mean it.
真的很美丽
I really like them.
谢谢
Thank you.
我也是真心的
I really mean it, too.
喂
Hey.
我需要这样的眼睛
I could use eyes like that.
我叫兰德
My name is Randoku.
你叫什么名字?
What is your name?
兰德
Randoku.
我喜欢这名字
I like that.
我叫泰瑞
I'm Terry.
跟我说说你的一切 泰瑞
Tell me all about yourself, Terry.
这只是我的一份暑期工
This is just a summer job for me.
-你在上大学? -是的
-You are in school? -Yeah.
我在大学读医学预科
Yeah. I'm pre-med at the university.
那么你有才学
So, you are smart.
可能吧
I guess.
这和两周前报失的货车相符
This matches the van that was reported stolen two weeks ago.
这里安全吗
Clear here?
是的 这里很安全
Yeah, it's clear here.
虽然我在这里打工
Mmm, you wouldn't really know it from meeting me in this place,
但我在班上名列前茅
but, I'm in the top one percent of my class.
真不错
I like that.
我们问问泰瑞是否知道什么
Let's see if Terry knows anything.
-嗨 泰瑞 -嗨
Hey, Terry. -Hey.
你们知不知道外面那辆货车…
Either of you wouldn't happen to know anything about that van…
不 我明白
No, no. I get it.
是来自非洲的巫医
It's a witch doctor from Africa…
-是的 -我凭什么
Yeah, -that's right. -And I should
要相信呢
believe this because what?
据麦克莱斯博士所说 他在为一个客户服务
According to Dr. Mackles, he's servicing a client.
嗯
Hmm.
你相信这套吗
You believe in this shit?
我回去工作了
You know what, I wanna go back to work.
喂 博伊德 坐下
Hey, Boyd. Sit down.
博伊德
Boyd!
我想他发现了什么
I think he's onto something.
发现了什么?
Yeah, like what?
上尉 我们有两名警员受伤
Captain, we have two officers down.
去找博伊德
Get Boyd.
你的名字是泰瑞吗
Is your name Terry?
小姐
Ma'am?
喂 没事的
Hey, it's okay.
我需要问你几个问题 好吗
I need to ask you a few questions, okay,
如果你能帮我回答
and if you can help me out with that,
或许我们能找到这个人
then maybe we can find this guy.
你会帮我吗 是吗
Are you gonna help me out? Yeah?
-好的 -是吗 好
-Sure. -Yeah? All right.
告诉我 他长什么样?
So, tell me, what, what did he look like?
他很高大吗
Was he big, tall, or what?
-他很高大 -是吗
-He was big. -Yeah?
很好
-Good. -Mm-hmm.
身高有没有超过六英尺
When you say big, like, over six feet, or what?
-我想是的 -嗯
-I think so. -Mm-hmm.
黑人? 白人?
Black? White? Where?
-他是个黑人 -哦
-He was a black guy. -He was.
有点帅
He was kind of handsome.
是的
Yeah.
而且 他的脸上有划痕
And, he was covered with scarification on his face.
他脸上有疤痕?
He had scarring on his face?
你知道他的名字吗
Did you get a name by any chance? Yeah?
他叫什么名字?
What was his name?
泰瑞 他叫什么名字?
Terry, what was his name?
兰德
Randoku.
-兰德? -兰德
-Randoku? -Randoku.
好
Okay.
来 我扶你起来
All right, come on. Let me get you up.
我扶你起来
Come on. Let me help you.
玛丽亚
Maria.
我们有名字了 兰德
We got a name. Randoku.
我们来查查吧
Go on, let's sort that out. Come on.
吉米 有发现吗
Jimmy, anything?
是的 很多东西
Yeah. Lots of anythings.
-是吗 -有拇指 食指 无名指指纹
-Yeah? -Got a thumb, forefinger, ring finger.
好
Okay.
还好他喜欢龙苦兰酒
Good thing your boy likes tequila.
-他大概6.3英尺 还是6.4英尺? -我估计6.4英尺
You're saying he's about 6, 6'3", 6'4" maybe?6'4", I would say, yeah.
吉米 查查是谁的指纹
Jimmy, give me a name on these prints.
他脸上奇怪的伤疤
These weird, uh, scars on his face.
脸上有伤疤 谢谢你 博伊德
Scars on his face. Thank you. Thank you. Boyd.
这位女士说她刚看到一个黑人
This lady said she just seen a black guy coming in and out
进入那栋在建公寓楼
of that unfinished apartment building.
几天前也看到他
Hadn't seen him around until a few days ago.
说他脸上有伤疤
Said he has scars on his face.
就是他我们走
That's our guy. Come on, let's go.
喂 基思
Hey, Keith.
小心前面 我们走 快
Watch the front. Let's go. Come on.
快 快走
Come on. Gotta go! Gotta go!
所有人都上二楼
I want everybody on two.
我们多交流
And let's communicate.
好的
Roger that.
-鲍比 你留在这里 -好
Bobby, -you stay here. -Copy that.
他来过这里
He's been here.
操
Fuck.
他在那里
There he goes!
他回到三楼了
Shit! He's coming back on the third floor.
不许动 克劳森 趴下
Freeze! Claussen get the fuck down!
有警员受伤 警员受伤
Officer down. Officer down!
该死的
Son of a bitch!
后援 现在跟着我
Backup. Hang in with me now.
操 我们有警员受伤 快快快
Fuck! We got officers down. Go, go, go!
有警员受伤
Officer down. He's injured.
玛丽亚 我们离开这里 我们走吧
Maria, let's get out of here. Let's go.
玛丽亚 我们走吧
Maria, let's go.
我们走
Yo, let's go.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
我带你出去
Okay, I'm gonna get you out of here.
喂 把你的夹克给我
Hey, give me your fucking jacket!
快走 快走
Let's go. Let's go, let's go!
希望你能看到我所看不到的
I'm hoping you see something I wouldn't.
我试试看
I'll try.
你先请
After you.
你为什么来美国?
So why'd you come here to America?
为了新的开始吧
New start, I guess.
是吗 你有家人吗
Yeah? You got any family?
不 我的兄弟姐妹还在非洲
No. My brothers and sisters are still back in Africa.
看看这个
Take a look at this.
我父亲从事医学工作
My father worked in medicine.
他和部落一起工作
He worked with the tribes.
我妈妈跟他一起干
My mother worked with him.
嗯
Mmm.
很抱歉
Well, for what it's worth,
把你牵扯进来
I'm sorry I dragged you into this shit.
不 你没有歉意
No, you're not.
确实没有
You're right. I'm not.
在某些文化中
You know, in certain cultures,
我可以要你的头或身体的另一部分
I could have your head or another body part.
-是吗 -是的
-Is that right? -Yeah.
作为向我表示道歉
As an apology to make me feel better.
嗯
Mmm.
希腊 亚洲 某些非洲部落
Greece, Asia, certain African tribes.
如果一个部落的某个人
If a certain member of a tribe offended another member
由于过于干涉他人的私事而冒犯了他
by delving too deeply into his personal affairs,
酋长可以把那个人处死
the chief could have that person killed
并把他的身体器官作为礼物送出
and the body part delivered as a gift.
嗯
Hmm.
是一种解决争端的方式
A way of saying, problem solved.
幸好在这个国家是非法的
Well, thank God that ain't legal in this country.
否则我会整天邮寄尸体
I'd be mailing out body parts all day long.
需要什么就找我
Let me know if you need anything.
没发现
Nothing.
抱歉 警探
Sorry, Detective.
你还在这里?
You're still here?
这个混蛋杀了我的两个人
This fucker killed two of my men.
你还好吗
You're okay?
坦桑尼亚10名儿童为了器官被人杀害
Ten children in Tanzania kidnapped and killed for body parts.
在西班牙有十几个孩子
A dozen children in Spain.
全欧洲有上千儿童失踪
Thousand of children are missing all across Europe.
你说我好不好?
And you ask me how I'm doing?
你不能让它影响你
You can't let it get to you.
我也一直这么劝自己
That's what I keep telling myself.
但心要有多硬 才能活下去啊
But how hard does your heart have to get in order to live?
也许你应该回家
Maybe you should go home.
和你的家人在一起
Be with your family.
我的家人 是的
My family, yeah.
你说得对
You're right.
我觉得每个人都有这么一天
I think there comes a day in everyone's life where
意识到自己其实并不重要
they realize they don't really matter much.
无论自己的目标是什么
Whatever their goals are
都没有价值
really don't amount to shit.
那是非常悲伤的一天
And that is a very sad day.
哦 谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
你这人真难搞 卢卡斯
You're a fucking piece of work, Lucas.
-你是个… -我不想谈
You're a fucking… LUCAS: We're not doing this.
又不想谈了?
We're not doing this again? We're not doing this again?
你知道你不该做什么吗
You know what you're not gonna do it?
你又睡着了
You fell asleep again!
你又要睡觉了 是吗
You're gonna go sleep again, yeah?
就像你以前那样?
Yeah, like you did before?
拜托 你想让我说什么
Come on, what do you want me to say?
你这该死的
You fucking piece of… LUCAS: Come on.
-混蛋 -别这样
-Son of a bitch! Come on, come on.
我需要一些你的酒
I need some of your brew.
进来吧
Come on in.
怎么了? 你还好吗
What's going on? You doing okay?
是的
Yeah.
你从没去找那个心理医生吧
I take it you never saw that shrink, did you?
嗯
Mmm.
我想给你看些东西
There was something that I wanted to show you,
我前几天在兰德的公寓里找到的
I found in Randoku's apartment the other day.
看看这个 是法纳有限公司
Look at this. It's, uh, it's Farner Ltd.
这是一家价值数十亿美元的跨国大公司
It's a multibillion dollar, multinational, mega corporation.
你听说过吗…
-Good one. -Have you ever heard of…
法纳公司 我认识那个混蛋
Farner company. I know that asshole.
捐了很多钱
Donates a lot of money.
我不知道 我想问题是
I don't know. I guess the question is though
看这里报纸上说
is what they're talking about here is that
周二有一场重要的投票
there's a big vote Tuesday.
你认为这对他有多重要?
How important do you think this is to him?
等等
Hold.
我是卢卡斯
It's Lucas.
法医有所发现 我们马上就去 谢谢
They have something in forensics. We'll be right down. Thanks.
这是我从酒吧采集的指纹
I got this from the bar.
但在美国数据库里没有匹配的
But there were no matches in US database,
我就查了国际刑警组织 发现了这个
so, I checked Interpol, and I got this.
把两者叠加时
When I superimpose them,
这个人叫兰德
I give you one M'Gushu Randoku.
出生于南非 祖鲁血统
Born in South Africa, Zulu heritage.
说他最近去过罗马
Says he was in Rome recently.
他的入境口岸呢 在哪里?
What about his port of entry? Where was it?
呃
Uh…
一周前来到新奥尔良
Came into New Orleans a week ago.
还有别的吗
Anything else?
是的 这个兰德
Well, yeah. Old M'Gushu here?
已经死了六年了
Been dead for six years.
这是
Here's his
一位苏丹将军签署的死亡证明
death certificate signed by a Sudanese General.
这不等于他已经死了
That doesn't mean he's dead.
可能他在高层有朋友帮他开的假证明
It might just mean he has friends in high places who can help him disappear.
他没死 还没有
He ain't dead. Not yet.
喂 卢卡斯
Hey, Lucas.
什么
Yeah?
克什怎么样了?
How's Kersch?
她正在生死线上挣扎 克劳森
She's fighting for her life, Claussen.
看看这个
Check this out.
这是在兰德的住处找到的
This was in Randoku's place.
-操 -不知道是怎么回事
-Shit. -Not sure what it's about.
我会调查一下 谢谢
You know what, I'll look -into it, thanks. -All right.
不用谢
You got it.
你懂英语吗
Do you speak English?
是的 我能帮你吗
Yes. Can I help you?
我是卢卡斯·博伊德警探 我从美国打的电话
This is Detective Lucas Boyd. I'm calling from America.
我要找一位警督 马里奥·拉瓦兹
I need to speak to a uh, I think it's Inspector, uh, Mario Lavazzi?
抱歉 他今天休息 警探
I'm sorry, but he's left for the day, Detective.
你不知道 这是紧急情况
Okay, well, you don't understand. This is an emergency.
我在调查一起两个孩子的谋杀案
I'm investigating a murder of two children.
希望能接通他的手机或家庭电话
Now, I'd love if you could get him on the cell phone or his home.
我不管他在哪里 给他打电话
I don't give a fuck where he is. Just call him.
好的 我找到他了
Okay, okay. Scusi. I find him.
-喂 -拉瓦兹警督吗
Si? Inspector Lavazzi?
-是的 -我是卢卡斯·博伊德警探
Yes. LUCAS: I'm Detective Lucas Boyd.
我在调查一起两个孩子的谋杀案
I'm investigating a murder of two children.
我们要找的一个嫌疑犯
Um, one of the suspects that we're looking for
是一个叫兰德的人
is a man by the name of M'Gushu Randoku.
他在美国杀了两个孩子
He's killed two children here in America.
有意思的是 我们在他的公寓看到了你的名片
The interesting thing is we found your card at his apartment.
有什么原因吗
Is there a reason for that?
他在欧洲各处绑架年轻女子
He was kidnapping young women all throughout Europe.
你说什么
Whoa, what'd you say?
他在全欧洲绑架年轻女性 警探
He was kidnapping young women all throughout Europe, Detective.
几周前我在罗马差点抓到他
I almost caught him here in Rome a few weeks ago.
但是那个狗娘养的跑了
But the son of a bitch got away.
好 你能帮我什么吗
Okay, well, is there anything you can help me with?
他在这里也做着同样的事情
Because he's doing the same thing here.
我知道他为谁效力
I know who he works for.
谁
Who?
我无法证明 是凭警察的直觉
I can't prove it. I know it as a cop.
好 那就像警察一样跟我说话
Yeah, okay, well, just talk to me like a cop then.
我们发现了一些监控录像 是兰德
We found some CCTV footage of Randoku meeting
和一个南非商人会面
with a South African businessman.
我后来发现了他的身份
I later found out his identity.
他叫谢尔比·法纳
His name is Shelby Farner.
F-A-R-N-E-R…
F-A-R-N-E-R.
法纳
Farner.
非常感谢
I appreciate it.
谢谢
Thank you.
不用谢 警探
Prego, Detective. Prego.
-我能帮你吗 -是的 夫人 我是博伊德警探
-Can I help you? -Yes, ma'am. I'm Detective Boyd.
谢尔比·法纳在吗
Is Shelby Farner around?
是的
Yes, he is.
-请帮我去找他 -好
Go get him for me, please. -All right. -Okay.
-法纳先生? -是的
Mr. Farner? -Yes.
我是博伊德警探 我们能谈谈吗
Detective Boyd. Do you mind if we have a word?
好的
Certainly. Uh…
-跟我来 -谢谢
-Come with me. I appreciate that. Thank you.
-你干什么 -你再敢碰城市里的另一个孩子
-What are you doing? -You touch another fucking kid in my city,
我会一枪崩了你
and I'm gonna fucking put a bullet in your head.
-你胡说什么 -我会一枪崩了你
-What are you talking about? -I'm gonna put a fucking bullet in your head.
听见了吗
You hear me?
你显然不知道我是什么身份
Obviously, you don't know who you're talking to.
你想要个强壮的人吗
You want somebody strong?
想要强壮的人 就来抓我
You want somebody strong, you come get me.
我就在这里
I'm right here.
我要告诉你
You know, I'm gonna tell you something.
在我抓到你的同伙之后
After I get your fucking partner,
我会来找你 知道我会做什么吗
I'm coming after you. And you know what I'm gonna do?
我会吃了你的肝
I'm gonna fucking eat your liver.
我是带着敬意而来
不要再帮那个警探了
没错
Exactly, yeah.
好了 女生们 该准备一下了
All right, ladies. Time to get ready.
各就各位 热身
Get on your numbers. Warm up.
在场边的女生们 热身
Ladies on the sideline, warm up.
预备
Set!
喔
Whoo!
-厉害 厉害 -谢谢
-Good job, good job! -Thank you.
喔
Whoo!
厉害 击掌
Good job. High five!
厉害 太棒了
Good job. Awesome.
你好
Hello.
我刚刚被兰德先生威胁了
I just got threatened by Mr. Randoku.
我很遗憾 麦克莱斯博士
I'm sorry to hear that, Dr. Mackles.
我不后悔
I'm not sorry.
去他的
Fuck him.
-来接我 -我马上就来 好
Pick me up. I'll be right there, yeah.
我听说你是很好的学生运动员
I hear you're quite the student athlete.
我尽力 先生
I try my best, sir.
你知道我有基金会
Do you know that I have a foundation
-为你这样的女生提供奖学金吗 -真的吗
Really?that offers scholarships for girls like you?
你喜欢比赛吗
Well, do you enjoy competition?
-哦 是的 -总是吗
-Oh, yeah. -Always?
是的
Yeah, I mean,
我们的教练说获胜不是最重要的
our coach tells us that winning isn't everything,
重要的是尽最大努力
but that giving it your best is what it's all about.
如果不想获胜 那又何必
What's the point of putting in all that work
努力训练呢
if you're not trying to win?
凯蒂 你真讨人喜欢
Ah, Katie, you are just delightful.
你肯定是个优等生
I'll bet you're a straight A student.
-是的 全优 -很好
-Yes, sir. Straight A's. -Delightful.
你最喜欢的科目是…
And your favorite subject is…
数学和科学都很喜欢
A tie between math and science.
但我也喜欢音乐
But I love music, too.
数学显然是音乐的重要组成部分 所以:
And math is obviously a big part of music, so…
很显然
Obviously.
你是怎么认识我父母的?
So, how do you know my parents?
我们已经认识多年了
Oh, we've known each other for ages.
好奇怪
So weird.
他们从未提过你
They never mentioned you before.
我很难相信
Well, I find that difficult to believe.
-他们真没说过 -拜托
-They really haven't. -Oh, come on!
真的
Really.
啊 凯蒂 我无法形容你有多完美
Ah, Katie. I can't tell you how perfect you are.
谢谢
Thank you!
给凯蒂准备一下
Let's get Katie ready.
准备什么
Ready for what?
哦
Oh…
这是一个惊喜
It's a surprise.
她叫凯蒂
Her name's Katie.
他们是如何处理的?
How are they dealing with it?
联邦调查局的老规矩
Well, usual. Fed playbook.
-劫匪没打来电话 -嗯
-No calls. -Mm-hmm.
没有赎金要求
No ransom demand.
我要告诉他们兰德的事
I need to tell them about Randoku.
是的 你把他们
Yeah. Well, when you do,
带去另一个房间说好吗
just take them into the other room, all right?
就是他
It's him.
是啊
Yeah, I know.
-我能提个建议吗 -好的
Can I make -a suggestion? -Sure, yeah.
-如果他为法纳工作 -嗯
If he is working for Farner… Mm-hmm.
他们要在一个非常安全的地方举行仪式
…they're gonna want to do the ceremony at a very safe place.
所以要寻找法纳的房产
So I would look for properties owned by Farner.
尤其是仓库式的房产 靠近水边的
Especially warehouse-type near water.
嗯
Mmm.
给我点好消息 克劳森
Give me some good news, Claussen.
法纳工业在本市拥有大量地产
Farner Industries owns a lot of property in town.
他们在河边有一个仓库
They got one warehouse by the river.
我现在把地址发给你
I'm sending you the address now.
好的 谢谢
Got it. Thanks.
你必须留在这里
You gotta stay here.
好
Okay.
Humu mimi nitakamata tani.
Humu mimi kuwa tani.
Humu kuwa tani.
Humu mimi nitakamata tani.
请住手
Please stop!
Humu mimi kuwa tani.
Humu mimi nitakamata tani.
不
No.
Humu mimi kuwa tani.
Humu mimi nitakamata tani.
把刀放下
Drop the fucking knife!
马上
Do it now!
否则我一枪崩了你
Do it now or I'll blow your fucking head off.
很好
Good.
手放在头上
Now put your hands behind your head.
不
No!
放弃吧
Give up!
我警告过你
I warned you.
不
No.
请不要
Please, no.
不
No.
是谁啊
Who's there?
博伊德警探
Detective Boyd.
现场发现一名白人男子死亡
One white male found dead on site.
谢尔比·法纳
Shelby Farner.
没有兰德的踪迹
No trace of Randoku.
博伊德警探
Detective Boyd.
我是拉瓦兹督察
This is Inspector Lavazzi.
拉瓦兹督察
Inspector Lavazzi.
我发现了一些可能有用的情况
I found something that might be helpful.
什么
What?
兰德曾在罗马
Randoku was here in Rome
参加了一个来自你的城市的人的讲座
attending a lecture from someone from your city.
一位名叫麦克莱斯的大学教授
A college professor by the name of Mackles.
这是九个月前的事
All of this happened nine months ago.
他们在讲座之后还见过几次面
They also met several times -after the lecture. -Mm-hmm.
对
Right.
也许这能帮到你
Maybe this can help you somehow.
感谢你的来电
I appreciate the call.
天
Aw, man.
该死的
God damn it.
好
All right.
-警探 -是的
Detective? -Mmm, yeah.
侦探? 你还好吗
Detective? Are you okay?
她是我的搭档
She was my partner.
没事的 她被转移了
It's all right. She's been transferred.
你说什么
What did you say?
没事的 她没事了
It's okay. She's okay.
-我把她转移到楼下了 -你什么意思?
I had her moved -downstairs. -No, no. What do you mean?
没事的 我把她转移到楼下了 警探
It's okay. I had her moved downstairs, Detective.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
没事的 会没事的
It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
-谢谢你 -医学奇迹时有发生
-Oh, thank you. -You know, every once in a while, there's a miracle.
是啊
I guess so. Yeah.
她的一个朋友昨晚来了 呆了大约一个小时
You know, a friend of hers came by last night and stayed for about an hour.
然后我看见他离开了
And then I saw him leave.
你什么意思? 他长什么样
What do you mean? What did he look like?
他是个高个子 头发花白的黑人
Um, he was a tall, greying black man.
大概70岁左右吧
Probably about 70s.
有着非常善良的眼睛
With very kind eyes.
他好像为她祈涛 然后我看见他离开了
I think he prayed over her, and then I saw him leave.
他说了什么
What did he say?
他只是说她会没事的
He just said she was going to be all right.
然后他说了一句我听不懂的话
And then he said a word I didn't understand.
说了什么
Yeah, what was that?
Muti
Muti?
-我不懂 -谢谢你救了她 医生
-I don't know. -Thank you for saving her, Doctor.
-不客气 -谢谢你
-You're welcome. -Thank you.
好的
You bet.
你好 这里是麦克莱斯博士的办公室
Hello, you've reached Dr. Mackles office.
麦克莱斯博士正在休长假
Dr. Mackles is on extended leave until further notice.
请留言
Please leave a message.
厉害
Well played.
你这人真难搞卢卡斯
You're a fucking piece of work, Lucas.
-你是个… -我不想谈
You're fucking… LUCAS: We're not doing this.
又不想谈了?
We're not doing this again? We're not doing this again?
你知道你不该做什么吗 你又睡着了
You know what you're not gonna do it? You fell asleep again!
你知道我们女儿有癫痛 你却睡着了
You know our daughter has fucking seizures, and you fell asleep!
你想让我说什么
What do I want?
你这该死的
Fucking piece of… LUCAS: Come on.
-混蛋 -别这样
-Son of a bitch! Come on, come on.
对不起
I'm sorry.
-我受够了 -上楼去
That's right, -I'm fucking done! -Go upstairs!
她是这个肮脏世界上唯一的美好
She was the only thing in this whole sick fucking world
你却把她夺走了
that was any good and you took her away from me!
迪莉
Deelie.
Deelie!
迪莉
我为我所做的事感到抱歉
I'm really sorry for what I did.